<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="httpErrorBadUrl">The page could not be opened because the URL is invalid.</string>
    <string name="httpErrorUnsupportedScheme">The protocol is not supported.</string>
    <string name="untitled">&lt;untitled></string>
    <string name="VideoView_error_text_unknown">Sorry, this video cannot be played.</string>
    <string name="VideoView_error_text_invalid_progressive_playback">Sorry, this video is not valid for streaming to this device.</string>
    <string name="mmiFdnError">Operation is restricted to fixed dialling numbers only.</string>
    <string name="badPin">The old PIN you typed is not correct.</string>
    <string name="badPuk">The PUK you typed is not correct.</string>
    <string name="mismatchPin">"The PINs that you typed don't match."</string>
    <string name="invalidPuk">Type a PUK that is 8 numbers long or more.</string>
    <string name="CLIRPermanent">The caller ID setting cannot be changed.</string>
    <string name="RestrictedOnAllVoice">All Voice services are blocked.</string>
    <string name="RestrictedOnVoiceData">Voice/Data services are blocked.</string>
    <string name="RestrictedOnAll">All Voice/Data/SMS services are blocked.</string>
    <string name="httpErrorUnsupportedAuthScheme">The site authentication scheme is not supported.</string>
    <string name="httpErrorFailedSslHandshake">A secure connection could not be established.</string>
    <string name="httpErrorFile">The file could not be accessed.</string>
    <string name="httpErrorFileNotFound">The requested file was not found.</string>
    <string name="notification_title">Sign-in error for %1$s</string>
    <string name="low_memory">Phone storage is full! Delete some files to free space.</string>
    <string name="shutdown_progress">Shutting down…</string>
    <string name="reboot_safemode_confirm">Do you want to reboot into safe mode? This will disable all third-party applications that you have installed. They will be restored when you reboot again.</string>
    <string name="no_recent_tasks">No recent applications.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_messages">Read and write your SMS, e-mail, and other messages.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_personalInfo">Direct access to information about you, stored on your contact card.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_location">Monitor your physical location</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_affectsBattery">Use features that can drain battery quickly.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_screenlock">Ability to affect behaviour of the lock screen on your device</string>
    <string name="permgrouplab_appInfo">Your application information</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_appInfo">Ability to affect behaviour of other applications on your device.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_systemClock">Change the device time or time zone.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_developmentTools">Features only needed for application developers.</string>
    <string name="permgroupdesc_accessibilityFeatures">Features that accessibility technology can request</string>
    <string name="capability_desc_canRetrieveWindowContent">"Inspect the content of a window that you're interacting with"</string>
    <string name="capability_desc_canRequestTouchExploration">Touched items will be spoken aloud and the screen will be able to be explored using gestures.</string>
    <string name="capability_title_canRequestEnhancedWebAccessibility">Turn on enhanced web accessibility</string>
    <string name="capability_desc_canRequestEnhancedWebAccessibility">Scripts may be installed to make app content more accessible.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_statusBar">Allows application to disable the status bar or add and remove system icons.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_statusBarService">Allows the application to be the status bar.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_expandStatusBar">Allows application to expand or collapse the status bar.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_processOutgoingCalls">Allows the app to process outgoing calls and change the number to be dialled. This permission allows the app to monitor, redirect or prevent outgoing calls.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveSms">Allows the app to receive and process SMS messages. This means that the app could monitor or delete messages sent to your device without showing them to you.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveMms">Allows the app to receive and process MMS messages. This means that the app could monitor or delete messages sent to your device without showing them to you.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveEmergencyBroadcast">Allows application to receive and process emergency broadcast messages. This permission is only available to system applications.</string>
    <string name="permlab_readCellBroadcasts">read mobile broadcast messages</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readCellBroadcasts">Allows the app to read mobile broadcast messages received by your device. Mobile broadcast alerts are delivered in some locations to warn you of emergency situations. Malicious apps may interfere with the performance or operation of your device when an emergency mobile broadcast is received.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_sendSms">Allows the app to send SMS messages. This may result in unexpected charges. Malicious apps may cost you money by sending messages without your confirmation.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_sendRespondViaMessageRequest">Allows the app to send requests to other messaging apps to handle respond-via-message events for incoming calls.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSms">Allows application to write to SMS messages stored on your phone or SIM card. Malicious applications may delete your messages.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveWapPush">Allows the app to receive and process WAP messages. This permission includes the ability to monitor or delete messages sent to you without showing them to you.</string>
    <string name="permlab_getTasks">retrieve running applications</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getTasks">Allows the app to retrieve information about currently running and recently run tasks. This may allow the app to discover information about which applications are used on the device.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_interactAcrossUsers">Allows the app to perform actions across different users on the device. Malicious apps may use this to violate the protection between users.</string>
    <string name="permlab_interactAcrossUsersFull">full licence to interact across users</string>
    <string name="permdesc_interactAcrossUsersFull">Allows all possible interactions across users.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getDetailedTasks">Allows the app to retrieve detailed information about currently running and recently run tasks. Malicious apps may discover private information about other apps.</string>
    <string name="permlab_reorderTasks">reorder running applications</string>
    <string name="permdesc_reorderTasks">Allows the app to move tasks to the foreground and background. The app may do this without your input.</string>
    <string name="permlab_removeTasks">stop running applications</string>
    <string name="permdesc_removeTasks">Allows an application to remove tasks and kill their applications. Malicious applications can disrupt the behaviour of other applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_manageActivityStacks">Allows the app to add, remove and modify the activity stacks which other apps run in. Malicious apps may disrupt the behaviour of other apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setScreenCompatibility">Allows the app to control the screen compatibility mode of other applications. Malicious applications may break the behaviour of other applications.</string>
    <string name="permlab_setDebugApp">enable application debugging</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setDebugApp">Allows an application to turn on debugging for another application. Malicious applications can use this to kill other applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeConfiguration">Allows an application to change the current configuration, such as the locale or overall font size.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_enableCarMode">Allows an application to enable the car mode.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_killBackgroundProcesses">Allows the app to end background processes of other apps. This may cause other apps to stop running.</string>
    <string name="permlab_forceStopPackages">force-stop other apps</string>
    <string name="permdesc_forceStopPackages">Allows an application to forcibly stop other applications.</string>
    <string name="permlab_forceBack">force application to close</string>
    <string name="permdesc_forceBack">Allows an application to force any activity that is in the foreground to close and go back. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_dump">Allows application to retrieve internal state of the system. Malicious applications may retrieve a wide variety of private and secure information that they should never normally need.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_retrieve_window_content">Allows application to retrieve the content of the active window. Malicious applications may retrieve the entire window content and examine all its text except passwords.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_temporary_enable_accessibility">Allows an application to temporarily enable accessibility on the device. Malicious apps may enable accessibility without user consent.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_magnify_display">Allows an application to magnify the content of a display. Malicious apps may transform the display content in a way that renders the device unusable.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_shutdown">Puts the activity manager into a shutdown state. Does not perform a complete shutdown.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_stopAppSwitches">Prevents the user from switching to another application.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getTopActivityInfo">Allows the holder to retrieve private information about the current application in the foreground of the screen.</string>
    <string name="permlab_runSetActivityWatcher">monitor and control all application launching</string>
    <string name="permdesc_runSetActivityWatcher">Allows an application to monitor and control how the system launches activities. Malicious applications may completely compromise the system. This permission is only needed for development, never for normal use.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_broadcastPackageRemoved">Allows an application to broadcast a notification that an application package has been removed. Malicious applications may use this to kill any other running application.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_broadcastSmsReceived">Allows an application to broadcast a notification that an SMS message has been received. Malicious applications may use this to forge incoming SMS messages.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_broadcastWapPush">Allows an application to broadcast a notification that a WAP PUSH message has been received. Malicious applications may use this to forge MMS message receipt or to silently replace the content of any web page with malicious variants.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setProcessLimit">Allows an application to control the maximum number of processes that will run. Never needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permlab_setAlwaysFinish">make all background applications close</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setAlwaysFinish">Allows an application to control whether activities are always finished as soon as they go to the background. Never needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_batteryStats">Allows an application to read the current low-level battery use data. May allow the application to find out detailed information about which apps you use.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_updateBatteryStats">Allows the app to modify collected battery statistics. Not for use by normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getAppOpsStats">Allows the app to retrieve collected application operation statistics. Not for use by normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_updateAppOpsStats">Allows the app to modify collected application operation statistics. Not for use by normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_backup">"Allows the application to control the system's backup and restore mechanism. Not for use by normal applications."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_confirm_full_backup">Allows the application to launch the full backup confirmation UI. Not to be used by any application.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_internalSystemWindow">Allows the app to create windows that are intended to be used by the internal system user interface. Not for use by normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_systemAlertWindow">Allows the app to draw on top of other applications or parts of the user interface. They may interfere with your use of the interface in any application, or change what you think you are seeing in other applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setAnimationScale">Allows an application to change the global animation speed (faster or slower animations) at any time.</string>
    <string name="permlab_manageAppTokens">manage application tokens</string>
    <string name="permdesc_manageAppTokens">Allows applications to create and manage their own tokens, bypassing their normal Z-ordering. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_freezeScreen">Allows the application to temporarily freeze the screen for a full-screen transition.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_injectEvents">Allows an application to deliver its own input events (key presses, etc.) to other applications. Malicious applications can use this to take over the phone.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readInputState">Allows the app to watch the keys that you press even when interacting with another app (such as typing a password). Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindInputMethod">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of an input method. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindAccessibilityService">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of an accessibility service. Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindPrintService">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a print service. Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindPrintSpoolerService">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a print spooler service. Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindNfcService">Allows the holder to bind to applications that are emulating NFC cards. Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindTextService">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a text service(e.g. SpellCheckerService). Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindVpnService">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a Vpn service. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindWallpaper">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a wallpaper. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindRemoteDisplay">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a remote display. Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindRemoteViews">Allows the holder to bind to the top-level interface of a widget service. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindDeviceAdmin">Allows the holder to send intents to a device administrator. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_manageDeviceAdmins">Allows the holder to add or remove active device administrators. Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setOrientation">Allows an application to change the rotation of the screen at any time. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setPointerSpeed">Allows an application to change the mouse or trackpad pointer speed at any time. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setKeyboardLayout">Allows the app to change the keyboard layout. Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permlab_signalPersistentProcesses">send Linux signals to applications</string>
    <string name="permdesc_signalPersistentProcesses">Allows the app to request that the supplied signal be sent to all persistent processes.</string>
    <string name="permlab_persistentActivity">make application always run</string>
    <string name="permdesc_persistentActivity">Allows the app to make parts of itself persistent in memory. This can limit the memory available to other apps, slowing down the phone.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_deletePackages">Allows an application to delete Android packages. Malicious applications can use this to delete important applications.</string>
    <string name="permlab_clearAppUserData">"delete other applications' data"</string>
    <string name="permdesc_clearAppUserData">Allows an application to clear user data.</string>
    <string name="permlab_deleteCacheFiles">"delete other applications' caches"</string>
    <string name="permdesc_deleteCacheFiles">Allows an application to delete cache files.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getPackageSize">Allows an application to retrieve its code, data, and cache sizes</string>
    <string name="permlab_installPackages">directly install applications</string>
    <string name="permdesc_installPackages">Allows an application to install new or updated Android packages. Malicious applications can use this to add new applications with arbitrarily powerful permissions.</string>
    <string name="permlab_clearAppCache">delete all application cache data</string>
    <string name="permdesc_clearAppCache">Allows the app to free phone storage by deleting files in the cache directories of other applications. This may cause other applications to start up more slowly as they need to re-retrieve their data.</string>
    <string name="permlab_movePackage">Move application resources</string>
    <string name="permdesc_movePackage">Allows an application to move application resources from internal to external media and vice versa.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readLogs">"Allows an application to read from the system's various log files. This allows it to discover general information about what you are doing with the phone, potentially including personal or private information."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_anyCodecForPlayback">Allows an application to use any installed media decoder to decode for playback.</string>
    <string name="permlab_changeComponentState">enable or disable application components</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeComponentState">"Allows an application to change whether a component of another application is enabled or not. Malicious applications can use this to disable important phone capabilities. Care must be used with this permission, as it is possible to get application components into an unusable, inconsistent or unstable state. "</string>
    <string name="permdesc_grantRevokePermissions">Allows an application to grant or revoke specific permissions for it or other applications. Malicious applications may use this to access features for which you have not granted them permission.</string>
    <string name="permlab_setPreferredApplications">set preferred applications</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setPreferredApplications">Allows the app to modify your preferred apps. Malicious apps may silently change the apps that are run, spoofing your existing apps to collect private data from you.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSettings">"Allows an application to modify the system's settings data. Malicious applications can corrupt your system's configuration."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSecureSettings">"Allows an application to modify the system's secure settings data. Not for use by normal applications."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeGservices">Allows an application to modify the Google services map. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permlab_receiveBootCompleted">run at start-up</string>
    <string name="permdesc_receiveBootCompleted">Allows an application to start itself as soon as the system has finished booting. This can make it take longer to start the phone and allow the application to slow down the phone overall by always running.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_broadcastSticky">Allows the app to send sticky broadcasts, which remain after the broadcast ends. Excessive use may make the phone slow or unstable by causing it to use too much memory.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readContacts">"Allows the app to read data about your contacts stored on your phone, including the frequency with which you've called, emailed or communicated in other ways with specific individuals. This permission allows apps to save your contact data, and malicious apps may share contact data without your knowledge."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeContacts">"Allows the app to modify the data about your contacts stored on your phone, including the frequency with which you've called, emailed or communicated in other ways with specific contacts. This permission allows apps to delete contact data."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readCallLog">"Allows the app to read your phone's call log, including data about incoming and outgoing calls. This permission allows apps to save your call log data, and malicious apps may share call log data without your knowledge."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeCallLog">"Allows the app to modify your phone's call log, including data about incoming and outgoing calls. Malicious apps may use this to erase or modify your call log."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readProfile">Allows the application to read personal profile information stored on your device, such as your name and contact information. This means the application can identify you and send your profile information to others.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeProfile">Allows the application to change or add to personal profile information stored on your device, such as your name and contact information. This means other applications can identify you and send your profile information to others.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readSocialStream">Allows the app to access and sync social updates from you and your friends. Be careful when sharing information – this allows the app to read communications between you and your friends on social networks, regardless of confidentiality. Note: this permission may not be enforced on all social networks.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeSocialStream">Allows the app to display social updates from your friends. Be careful when sharing information – this allows the app to produce messages that may appear to come from a friend. Note: this permission may not be enforced on all social networks.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readCalendar">Allows the app to read all calendar events stored on your phone, including those of friends or colleagues. This may allow the app to share or save your calendar data, regardless of confidentiality or sensitivity.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeCalendar">"Allows the app to add, remove and change events that you can modify on your phone, including those of friends or colleagues. This may allow the app to send messages that appear to come from calendar owners, or modify events without the owners' knowledge."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessMockLocation">Create mock location sources for testing or install a new location provider. This allows the app to override the location and/or status returned by other location sources such as GPS or location providers.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessLocationExtraCommands">Allows the app to access extra location-provider commands. This may allow the app to interfere with the operation of the GPS or other location sources.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_installLocationProvider">Create mock location sources for testing or installing a new location provider. This allows the app to override the location and/or status returned by other location sources such as GPS or location providers.</string>
    <string name="permlab_accessFineLocation">precise location (GPS and network-based)</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessFineLocation">Allows the app to get your precise location using the Global Positioning System (GPS) or network location sources such as mobile phone masts and Wi-Fi. These location services must be turned on and available to your device for the app to use them. Apps may use this to determine where you are, and this may consume additional battery power.</string>
    <string name="permlab_accessCoarseLocation">approximate location (network-based)</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessCoarseLocation">Allows the app to get your approximate location. This location is derived by location services using network location sources such as mobile phone masts and Wi-Fi. These location services must be turned on and available to your device for the app to use them. Apps may use this to determine approximately where you are.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessSurfaceFlinger">Allows application to use SurfaceFlinger low-level features.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readFrameBuffer">Allows application to read the content of the frame buffer.</string>
    <string name="permlab_controlWifiDisplay">control Wi-Fi displays</string>
    <string name="permdesc_captureAudioHotword">Allows the app to capture audio for hotword detection. The capture can happen in the background but does not prevent other audio capture (e.g. Camcorder).</string>
    <string name="permdesc_mediaContentControl">Allows the app to control media playback and access the media information (title, author etc.).</string>
    <string name="permdesc_recordAudio">Allows the app to record audio with the microphone. This permission allows the app to record audio at any time without your confirmation.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_camera">Allows the app to take pictures and videos with the camera. This permission allows the app to use the camera at any time without your confirmation.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_cameraDisableTransmitLed">Allows a pre-installed system application to disable the indicator LED when the camera is in use.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_brick">Allows the application to disable the entire phone permanently. This is very dangerous.</string>
    <string name="permlab_mount_unmount_filesystems">access SD Card file system</string>
    <string name="permdesc_mount_unmount_filesystems">Allows the application to mount and unmount filesystems for removable storage.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_mount_format_filesystems">Allows the application to format removable storage.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_asec_access">Allows the application to get information on internal storage.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_asec_create">Allows the application to create internal storage.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_asec_destroy">Allows the application to destroy internal storage.</string>
    <string name="permlab_asec_mount_unmount">mount / unmount internal storage</string>
    <string name="permdesc_asec_mount_unmount">Allows the application to mount / unmount internal storage.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_asec_rename">Allows the application to rename internal storage.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_vibrate">Allows the application to control the vibrator.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_fm_radio_receiver">Allows the application to control the FM receiver.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_fm_radio_transmitter">Allows the application to control the FM transmitter.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_flashlight">Allows the application to control the flashlight.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_manageUsb">Allows the application to manage preferences and permissions for USB devices.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_hardware_test">Allows the application to control various peripherals for the purpose of hardware testing.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_callPhone">"Allows the app to call phone numbers without your intervention. This may result in unexpected charges or calls. Note that this doesn't allow the app to call emergency numbers. Malicious apps may cost you money by making calls without your confirmation."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_callPrivileged">Allows the application to call any phone number, including emergency numbers, without your intervention. Malicious applications may place unnecessary and illegal calls to emergency services.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_performCdmaProvisioning">Allows the application to start CDMA provisioning. Malicious applications may unnecessarily start CDMA provisioning</string>
    <string name="permdesc_locationUpdates">Allows the app to enable/disable location update notifications from the radio. Not for use by normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_checkinProperties">Allows read/write access to properties uploaded by the checkin service. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindGadget">Allows the application to tell the system which widgets can be used by which application. With this permission, applications can give access to personal data to other applications. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_modifyPhoneState">Allows the application to control the phone features of the device. An application with this permission can switch networks, turn the phone radio on and off and the like without ever notifying you.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readPhoneState">Allows the app to access the phone features of the device. This permission allows the app to determine the phone number and device IDs, whether a call is active, and the remote number connected by a call.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_wakeLock">Allows an application to prevent the phone from going to sleep.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_devicePower">Allows the application to turn the phone on or off.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_factoryTest">Run as a low-level manufacturer test, allowing complete access to the phone hardware. Only available when a phone is running in manufacturer test mode.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setWallpaper">Allows the application to set the system wallpaper.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setWallpaperHints">Allows the application to set the system wallpaper size hints.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_masterClear">Allows an application to completely reset the system to its factory settings, erasing all data, configuration, and installed applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setTime">"Allows an application to change the phone's clock time."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_setTimeZone">"Allows an application to change the phone's time zone."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_getAccounts">Allows the app to get the list of accounts known by the phone. This may include any accounts created by applications that you have installed.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_authenticateAccounts">Allows an application to use the account authenticator capabilities of the AccountManager, including creating accounts and getting and setting their passwords.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_manageAccounts">Allows an application to perform operations like adding, and removing accounts and deleting their password.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_useCredentials">Allows an application to request authentication tokens.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessNetworkState">Allows the app to view information about network connections such as which networks exist and are connected.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_createNetworkSockets">Allows the app to create network sockets and use customised network protocols. The browser and other applications provide means to send data to the Internet, so this permission is not required to send data to the Internet.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeApnSettings">Allows an application to change network settings and to intercept and inspect all network traffic, for example to change the proxy and port of any APN. Malicious applications could monitor, redirect or modify network packets without your knowledge.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeNetworkState">Allows an application to change the state of network connectivity.</string>
    <string name="permlab_changeTetherState">Change tethered connectivity</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeTetherState">Allows an application to change the state of tethered network connectivity.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeBackgroundDataSetting">Allows an application to change the background data usage setting.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessWifiState">Allows the app to view information about Wi-Fi networking, such as whether Wi-Fi is enabled and names of connected Wi-Fi devices.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeWifiState">Allows the app to connect to and disconnect from Wi-Fi access points and to make changes to device configuration for Wi-Fi networks.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeWifiMulticastState">Allows the app to receive packets sent to all devices on a Wi-Fi network using multicast addresses, not just your phone. It uses more power than the non-multicast mode.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bluetoothAdmin">Allows an application to configure the local Bluetooth phone, and to discover and pair with remote devices.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bluetoothPriv">Allows the app to pair with remote devices without user interaction.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_changeWimaxState">Allows the app to connect the phone to and disconnect the phone from WiMAX networks.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bluetooth">Allows the app to view the configuration of Bluetooth on the phone and to make and accept connections with paired devices.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_nfc">Allows an application to communicate with Near Field Communication (NFC) tags, cards and readers.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_disableKeyguard">Allows the app to disable the keylock and any associated password security. For example, the phone disables the keylock when receiving an incoming phone call, then re-enables the keylock when the call is finished.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readSyncStats">Allows an app to read the sync stats for an account, including the history of sync events and how much data is synced.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_subscribedFeedsRead">Allows an application to get details about the currently synced feeds.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_subscribedFeedsWrite">Allows the app to modify your currently synced feeds. Malicious apps may change your synced feeds.</string>
    <string name="permlab_readDictionary">"read terms you've added to the dictionary"</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readDictionary">Allows the app to read all words, names and phrases that the user may have stored in the user dictionary.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeDictionary">Allows an application to write new words into the user dictionary.</string>
    <string name="permlab_sdcardWrite">modify/delete SD card contents</string>
    <string name="permdesc_sdcardWrite">Allows an application to write to the SD card.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_mediaStorageWrite">Allows an application to modify the contents of the internal media storage.</string>
    <string name="permlab_cache_filesystem">access the cache file system</string>
    <string name="permdesc_cache_filesystem">Allows an application to read and write the cache file system.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_use_sip">Allows an application to use the SIP service to make/receive Internet calls.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readNetworkUsageHistory">Allows an application to read historical network usage for specific networks and applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_manageNetworkPolicy">Allows an application to manage network policies and define application-specific rules.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_modifyNetworkAccounting">Allows modification of how network usage is accounted against applications. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessNotifications">Allows the app to retrieve, examine and clear notifications, including those posted by other apps.</string>
    <string name="permlab_invokeCarrierSetup">invoke the operator-provided configuration app</string>
    <string name="permdesc_invokeCarrierSetup">Allows the holder to invoke the operator-provided configuration app. Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_limitPassword">Control the length and the characters allowed in screen-unlock passwords</string>
    <string name="policydesc_watchLogin">"Monitor the number of incorrect passwords typed when unlocking the screen and lock the phone or erase all the phone's data if too many incorrect passwords are typed."</string>
    <string name="policydesc_resetPassword">Change the screen-unlock password</string>
    <string name="policydesc_forceLock">Control how and when the screen locks</string>
    <string name="policydesc_wipeData">"Erase the phone's data without warning, by performing a factory data reset"</string>
    <string name="policydesc_setGlobalProxy">Set the device global proxy to be used while policy is enabled. Only the first device admin sets the effective global proxy.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_expirePassword">Control how frequently the lock-screen password must be changed</string>
    <string name="policydesc_encryptedStorage">"Require that stored application data be encrypted "</string>
    <string name="pinpuk_attempts">"
Attempts remaining: "</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_password_wrong">Sorry, try again</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_missing_sim_instructions">Please insert a SIM card.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_missing_sim_instructions_long">The SIM card is missing or not readable. Please insert a SIM card.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_sim_error_message_short">Invalid card.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_sim_unlock_progress_dialog_message">Unlocking SIM card…</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_failed_attempts_almost_glogin" formatted="false">"You have incorrectly drawn your unlock pattern %d times. After %d more unsuccessful attempts, you will be asked to unlock your phone using your Google sign-in.

Please try again in %d seconds."</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_failed_attempts_almost_at_wipe" formatted="false">You have incorrectly attempted to unlock the phone %d times. After %d more unsuccessful attempts, the phone will be reset to factory default and all user data will be lost.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_failed_attempts_now_wiping">You have incorrectly attempted to unlock the phone %d times. The phone will now be reset to factory default.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_glogin_too_many_attempts">Too many pattern attempts!</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_glogin_instructions">To unlock, sign in with your Google account</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_glogin_checking_password">Checking...</string>
    <string name="factorytest_not_system">The FACTORY_TEST action is only supported for packages installed in /system/app.</string>
    <string name="factorytest_no_action">No package was found that provides the FACTORY_TEST action.</string>
    <string name="js_dialog_title">"The page at '%s' says:"</string>
    <string name="double_tap_toast">Tip: double-tap to zoom in and out.</string>
    <string name="autofill_this_form">AutoFill</string>
    <string name="autofill_province">County</string>
    <string name="autofill_state">County</string>
    <string name="autofill_zip_code">Post code</string>
    <string name="permdesc_readHistoryBookmarks">"Allows the app to read the history of all URLs that the Browser has visited, and all of the Browser's bookmarks. Note: this permission may not be enforced by third-party browsers or other applications with web browsing capabilities."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeHistoryBookmarks">"Allows the app to modify the Browser's history or bookmarks stored on your device. This may allow the app to erase or modify Browser data. Note: this permission may not be enforced by third-party browsers or other applications with web-browsing capabilities."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_addVoicemail">Allows the application to add messages to your voicemail inbox.</string>
    <string name="permlab_writeGeolocationPermissions">Modify Browser geolocation permissions</string>
    <string name="permdesc_writeGeolocationPermissions">"Allows an application to modify the Browser's geolocation permissions. Malicious applications can use this to allow sending location information to arbitrary websites."</string>
    <string name="permdesc_packageVerificationAgent">Allows the application to verify a package is installable.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_bindPackageVerifier">Allows the holder to make requests of package verifiers. Should never be needed for normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_accessContentProvidersExternally">Allows the holder to access content providers from the shell. Should never be needed for normal apps.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_updateLock">Allows the holder to offer information to the system about when would be a good time for a non-interactive reboot to upgrade the device.</string>
    <string name="enable_explore_by_touch_warning_message">"%1$s wants to enable Explore by Touch. When Explore by Touch is turned on, you can hear or see descriptions of what's under your finger or perform gestures to interact with the phone."</string>
    <string name="replace">Replace…</string>
    <string name="app_running_notification_title">%1$s is running</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="chooseUsbActivity">Select an application for the USB device</string>
    <string name="noApplications">No applications can perform this action.</string>
    <string name="aerr_process">Unfortunately, the process %1$s has stopped.</string>
    <string name="anr_activity_application">"%2$s is not responding.

Would you like to close it?"</string>
    <string name="anr_activity_process">"Activity %1$s is not responding.

Would you like to close it?"</string>
    <string name="anr_application_process">%1$s is not responding. Would you like to close it?</string>
    <string name="anr_process">"Process %1$s is not responding.

Would you like to close it?"</string>
    <string name="launch_warning_title">Application redirected</string>
    <string name="smv_application">The application %1$s (process %2$s) has violated its self-enforced StrictMode policy.</string>
    <string name="smv_process">The process %1$s has violated its self-enforced StrictMode policy.</string>
    <string name="android_upgrading_title">Android is upgrading...</string>
    <string name="android_upgrading_apk">Optimising application %1$d of %2$d.</string>
    <string name="android_upgrading_starting_apps">Starting applications.</string>
    <string name="heavy_weight_switcher_title">Switch applications?</string>
    <string name="heavy_weight_switcher_text">Another application is already running that must be stopped before you can start a new one.</string>
    <string name="old_app_description">"Don't start the new application."</string>
    <string name="new_app_description">Stop the old application without saving.</string>
    <string name="wifi_available_sign_in">Sign in to Wi-Fi network</string>
    <string name="network_available_sign_in">Sign in to network</string>
    <string name="wifi_watchdog_network_disabled_detailed">" has a poor internet connection."</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_failed_message">"Couldn't start Wi-Fi Direct"</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_from_message">From:</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_to_message">To:</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_enter_pin_message">Type the required PIN:</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_show_pin_message">PIN:</string>
    <string name="sms_short_code_details">This <font fgcolor="#ffffb060">may cause charges</font> to your mobile account.</string>
    <string name="sms_premium_short_code_details"><font fgcolor="#ffffb060">This will cause charges to your mobile account.</font></string>
    <string name="sms_short_code_remember_undo_instruction">You can change this later in Settings > Apps</string>
    <string name="sim_added_message">You must restart your device to access the mobile network.</string>
    <string name="usb_storage_error_message">There is a problem using your SD card for USB mass storage.</string>
    <string name="usb_storage_stop_error_message">There was a problem turning off USB storage. Check to make sure you have unmounted the USB host, then try again.</string>
    <string name="dlg_confirm_kill_storage_users_text">"If you turn on USB storage, some apps that you're using will stop and may be unavailable until you turn off USB storage."</string>
    <string name="usb_notification_message">Touch for other USB options</string>
    <string name="ext_media_nofs_notification_message">SD card is blank or has unsupported file system.</string>
    <string name="ext_media_badremoval_notification_message">Note: Unmount SD card before removing it</string>
    <string name="activity_list_empty">No matching activities found</string>
    <string name="permdesc_copyProtectedData">Allows invoking of default container service to copy content. Not for use by normal applications.</string>
    <string name="permlab_control_keyguard">Control displaying and hiding of keyguard</string>
    <string name="grant_credentials_permission_message_header">The following one or more applications request permission to access your account, both now and in the future.</string>
    <string name="grant_permissions_header_text">Access Request</string>
    <string name="permission_request_notification_title">Permission Requested</string>
    <string name="permission_request_notification_with_subtitle">"Permission Requested
for account %s"</string>
    <string name="vpn_title">VPN is activated.</string>
    <string name="vpn_lockdown_connecting">Always-on VPN connecting…</string>
    <string name="throttle_warning_notification_title">High mobile data use</string>
    <string name="throttle_warning_notification_message">Touch to learn more about mobile data use</string>
    <string name="throttled_notification_message">Touch to learn more about mobile data use</string>
    <string name="progress_unmounting">Unmounting SD card...</string>
    <string name="progress_erasing">Erasing SD card...</string>
    <string name="format_error">Failed to erase SD card.</string>
    <string name="sync_too_many_deletes_desc">There are %1$d deleted items for %2$s, account %3$s. What would you like to do?</string>
    <string name="sync_really_delete">Delete the items.</string>
    <string name="sync_undo_deletes">Undo the deletes.</string>
    <string name="sync_do_nothing">Do nothing for now.</string>
    <string name="activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an application</string>
    <string name="keyboard_headset_required_to_hear_password">Plug in a headset to hear password keys spoken aloud.</string>
    <string name="storage_internal">Internal Storage</string>
    <string name="extract_edit_menu_button">Edit...</string>
    <string name="data_usage_warning_body">Touch to view usage and settings</string>
    <string name="data_usage_limit_body">Touch to enable</string>
    <string name="data_usage_limit_snoozed_body">%s over specified limit</string>
    <string name="org_name">Organisation:</string>
    <string name="org_unit">Organisational unit:</string>
    <string name="share_action_provider_share_with">Share with...</string>
    <string name="list_delimeter">", "</string>
    <string name="sending">Sending...</string>
    <string name="default_audio_route_name">Phones</string>
    <string name="media_route_chooser_searching">Searching for devices…</string>
    <string name="kg_forgot_pattern_button_text">Forgotten Pattern</string>
    <string name="kg_sim_unlock_progress_dialog_message">Unlocking SIM card…</string>
    <string name="kg_invalid_sim_pin_hint">Type a PIN that is 4 to 8 numbers long.</string>
    <string name="kg_login_account_recovery_hint">"Forgot your username or password?

Visit "<b>google.com/accounts/recovery</b>.</string>
    <string name="kg_login_checking_password">Checking account…</string>
    <string name="kg_too_many_failed_pin_attempts_dialog_message" formatted="false">"You have typed your PIN incorrectly %d times.

Try again in %d seconds."</string>
    <string name="kg_too_many_failed_password_attempts_dialog_message" formatted="false">"You have typed your password incorrectly %d times.

Try again in %d seconds."</string>
    <string name="kg_too_many_failed_pattern_attempts_dialog_message" formatted="false">"You have drawn your unlock pattern incorrectly %d times.

Try again in %d seconds."</string>
    <string name="kg_failed_attempts_almost_at_wipe" formatted="false">You have attempted to unlock the phone incorrectly %d times. After %d more unsuccessful attempts, the phone will be reset to factory default and all user data will be lost.</string>
    <string name="kg_failed_attempts_now_wiping">You have attempted to unlock the phone incorrectly %d times. The phone will now be reset to factory default.</string>
    <string name="kg_failed_attempts_almost_at_login" formatted="false">"You have drawn your unlock pattern incorrectly %d times. After %d more unsuccessful attempts, you will be asked to unlock your phone using an email account.

Try again in %d seconds."</string>
    <string name="kg_text_message_separator">" — "</string>
    <string name="safe_media_volume_warning">"Raise volume above recommended level?
Listening at high volume for long periods may damage your hearing."</string>
    <string name="enable_accessibility_canceled">Accessibility cancelled.</string>
    <string name="mediasize_japanese_hagaki">Hagaki</string>
    <string name="mediasize_japanese_oufuku">Oufuku</string>
    <string name="sound_level_alert_message">Listening to audio above the current volume level for a long period of time may damage your hearing.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_disableMountingExternalStorage">Prevent the SD card from being mounted in the device.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_localDesktopSync">Prevent Local Desktop Sync from being used on the device.</string>
    <string name="storage_disabled_notification_message">A security policy is restricting the use of the SD card.</string>
    <string name="wifi_disabled_notification_message">"A security policy is restricting the use of Wi-Fi. "</string>
    <string name="tethering_disabled_notification_message">A security policy is restricting the use of tethering.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_disabled_notification_message">A security policy is restricting the use of Bluetooth.</string>
    <string name="permlab_taskSwitcherPluginView">Provide plug-in view to the task-switcher</string>
    <string name="permdesc_taskSwitcherPluginView">Allows the application to provide a plug-in view to the task-switcher</string>
    <string name="internal_storage_factory_reset_shared">Internal storage is currently being used by a computer.</string>
    <string name="internal_storage_erase_data_desc">Are you sure you want to format internal storage? All data on it will be lost.</string>
    <string name="policydesc_encryptedSdcard">Require encryption of SD card</string>
    <string name="init_strings_init_mode_title_txt">Initialisation mode</string>
    <string name="init_strings_dialog_make_sure_title_txt">Initialising phone</string>
    <string name="policydesc_disableConsumerEmail">Prevent use of personal email</string>
    <string name="policydesc_disablePopImapEmail">Prevent use of POP/IMAP email</string>
    <string name="policylab_disableConsumerEmail">Disable personal email</string>
    <string name="policylab_disablePopImapEmail">Disable POP/IMAP email</string>
    <string name="ct_cplusw_notification_text">CT Wi-Fi network connected. Contact 10000 or local shop for billing info.</string>
    <string name="ct_cplusw_pppoe_connection_dialog_title">Poznámky</string>
    <string name="docomo_low_internal_storage_view_text">Your device is low on memory. Uninstall unused apps, otherwise some applications or functions may not work properly. To uninstall apps, go to Settings, select apps and tap Uninstall.</string>
    <string name="emmc_format_progress">Format internal storag.</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_strings_backup_question_3_txt">What is your favourite place?</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_strings_backup_question_4_txt">What is your favourite film?</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_strings_sim_puk_locked_message_txt">Enter the PUK code from your operator</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_strings_sim_puk_locked_out_message_txt">Please contact your operator</string>
    <string name="policydesc_allowHtmlEmail">Set whether the email synchronised to your phone can be in HTML format or just plain text</string>
    <string name="policydesc_controlCamera">"Control the usage of your phone's built-in camera"</string>
    <string name="policydesc_maximumCalendarAgeFilte">Set the maximum number of days that past calendars can be synchronised to your phone</string>
    <string name="policydesc_maximumEmailAge">Set the maximum number of days that past email can be synchronised to your phone</string>
    <string name="policydesc_maximumEmailBodySize">Set the maximum size beyond which email messages are truncated when they are synchronised to your phone</string>
</resources>
