<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Extended Standby Mode controller</string>
    <string name="description_msg_txt">"When the screen is off, Wi-Fi and mobile data will be temporarily disabled, and most applications will be inactive. You will still receive phone calls, SMS/MMS messages and, Sony™calendar notifications and Sony™ alarm signals. The music player and FM radio will work, and downloads and uploads in progress will be allowed to finish.

When the screen is on, your phone will function normally.
"</string>
    <string name="description_msg_no_telephony_txt">"When the screen is off, Wi-Fi will be temporarily disabled, and most applications will be inactive. You will still receive Sony™calendar notifications and Sony™ alarm signals. The music player and FM radio will work, and downloads and uploads in progress will be allowed to finish.

When the screen is on, your device will function normally."</string>
    <string name="low_battery_mode_description_msg_txt">"Enable Low battery mode to turn off power consuming features and settings when the battery is below a preset level. Tap Low battery mode to change settings.
"</string>
    <string name="xssm_blocker_detector_long_msg">If you use this application often, ignore this warning. If not, uninstall or force stop the application.</string>
    <string name="xssm_blocker_detector_ignore">"Got it. Don't show again."</string>
    <string name="network_detector_msg">%s is sending and receiving data while the screen is off and causes the battery to drain faster.</string>
    <string name="wakelock_detector_msg">%s has not been used in several weeks.</string>
    <string name="wakelock_detector_long_msg">It may wake the device from standby mode. Uninstalling it may improve device performance and extend battery time.</string>
    <string name="notification_dont_show_again">"Got it. Don't show again."</string>
    <string name="notification_text_ps">Activate Low battery mode</string>
    <string name="notification_descr_ps">Low battery mode can extend battery life by e.g. turning off Wi-Fi or reducing screen brightness when battery is low.</string>
    <string name="unused_application_ignore">"Got it. Don't show again."</string>
    <string name="drain_dialog_text_usb_txt">The connected power source is not sufficient. The battery is discharging faster than it is charging. Please change to your AC charger.</string>
    <string name="drain_dialog_text_wallcharger_txt">The connected power source is not sufficient. The battery is discharging faster than it is charging. Minimize your device usage while charging.</string>
    <string name="extend_battery_tip_dialog_headar">Power management tip</string>
    <string name="low_battery_mode_tip_dialog">Low battery mode can extend battery life by e.g. turning off Wi-Fi or reducing screen brightness when battery is low. Set up Low battery mode?</string>
    <string name="lowbattery_activated_notification">Low battery mode activated</string>
</resources>
